Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1139
    - Local 1139 R.W. Bergstrom Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1941 (Box 8, Folder 117)
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Brothers Boiler Negotiation and Boilermakers Inter-union Rivalry with Contract Proposal, March 28, 1939; 13.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding RR Howell Contract, May 11, 1939; 14.
      - Bergstrom to Carey Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, May 23, 1939; 15.
      - Bergstrom to Carey Regarding Olson Manufacturing and Crown Iron Negotiations, June 1, 1939; 16.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Brothers Boiler Strike and Boilermakers Inter-union Rivalry, June 8, 1939; 17.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Strike, June 10, 1939; 18.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Brown Sheet Iron Contract and Twentieth Century Brass Strike, June 13, 1939; 19.
      - Bergstrom to Carey Regarding North Star Foundry Negotiation, July 21, 1939; 20.
      - Bergstrom to Carey Regarding North Star Foundry Negotiation, July 27, 1939; 21.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Northwestern Smelting Contract, October 9, 1939; 22.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Ersham and RR Howell Organization, October 13, 1939; 23.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Union Label, October 20, 1939; 24.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Union Label, October 31, 1939; 25.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Brothers Boiler Negotiation, January 26, 1940; 26.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Brothers Boiler Negotiation, March 6, 1940; 27.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, April 8, 1940; 28.
      - Bergstrom to Carey Regarding Wages and Political Action, April 19, 1940; 29.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Foundries and Ornamental Iron Shops Negotiations, April 24, 1940; 30.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding North Star Specialty Manufacturing Contract, April 24, 1940; 31.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Hudson Subcontracting, May 2, 1940; 32.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Negotiations, May 8, 1940; 33.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, May 13, 1940; 34.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 10, 1940; 35.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries Negotiation, June 18, 1940; 36.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Crown Iron Negotiation, June 27, 1940; 37.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries Negotiation, July 2, 1940; 38.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Hart Carrier Contract, July 30, 1940; 39.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Dental Labs Organization, August 2, 1940; 40.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Remmington Rand Boycott, August 10, 1940; 41.
      - Bergstrom to Sidney Hillman Regarding Foundries Strike, August 13, 1940; 42.
      - Bergstrom to Carey Regarding Foundries Strike With Copy to Matles, August 19, 1940; 43.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Foundries Strike, August 20, 1940; 44.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Foundries, August 23, 1940; 45.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries Strike, October 2, 1940; 46.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Northwestern Smelting Contract, October 25, 1940; 47.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Salbert Iron Contract, November 8, 1940; 48.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Star Iron Works Contract, November 8, 1940; 49.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding North Star Contract, December 13, 1940; 50.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Nausel Foundry Contract and Molders Inter-union Rivalry, January 13, 1941; 51.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Negotiations, January 28, 1941; 52.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding US Air Conditioning, January 28, 1941; 53.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Sonneborn Sons, February 22, 1941; 54.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twin City Steel Contract, March 7, 1941; 55.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Brothers Boiler Negotiation, April 9, 1941; 56.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Stainless Steel Products Contract, April 14, 1941; 57.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, June 16, 1941; 58.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries Wages, June 24, 1941; 59.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Franklin Transformer Contract, June 24, 1941; 60.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Contract, July 17, 1941; 61.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Brothers Boiler Contract, August 7, 1941; 62.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Lockout, September 15, 1941; 63.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Telex Products Contract, September 19, 1941; 64.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Stookland Road Machinery Contract, September 20, 1941; 65.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Lockout, September 30, 1941; 66.
    - Local 1139 R.W. Bergstrom Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 8, Folder 118)
      - R.W. Bergstrom to James Matles Regarding Progress Pattern Contract, October 9, 1941; 1.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Contracts, October 9, 1941; 2.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Silen Sales and Williams Novelty Contracts, October 29, 1941; 3.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Smith Heating Contract, October 29, 1941; 4.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Photoplating Contract, October 29, 1941; 5.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Hudson Manufacturing Contract, November 5, 1941; 6.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundry Industry Organization, November 11, 1941; 7.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries and Molders Inter-union Rivalry, January 23, 1942; 8.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries, Molders Inter-union Rivalry, and Negotiations, February 17, 1942; 9.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Negotiations, February 27, 1942; 10.
      - Bergstrom to J.R. Steelman Regarding US Air Conditioning Negotiation, March 2, 1942; 11.
      - Bergstrom to Julius Emspak Regarding Minneapolis Electric Steel, March 12, 1942; 12.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Butler Manufacturing Contract, March 18, 1942; 13.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Union Shop, April 18, 1942; 14.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Twin City Steel Contract, April 27, 1942; 15.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Foundries Negotiation, May 4, 1942; 16.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Franklin Transformer Negotiation, June 18, 1942; 17.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Negotiations, May 11, 1943; 18.
      - Bergstrom to John Meyer Regarding North Star Foundry and Dues Check-off, August 10, 1943; 19.
      - Bergstrom to Gus Towsen Regarding Wages, February 28, 1944; 20.
      - Bergstrom to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Hart Carler Negotiation and War Labor Board, August 29, 1945; 21.
      - Bergstrom to Fitzgerald Regarding US Air Conditioning Negotiation, March 21, 1946; 22.
      - Bergstrom to Fitzgerald Regarding Telex Strike, June 4, 1946; 23.
      - Bergstrom to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Toro Manufacturing with Competitors List, July 11, 1946; 24.
      - Bergstrom to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Local 203, February 17, 1947; 25.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Hoff Rubber and Despatch Oven Strikes, August 8, 1947; 26.
      - Bergstrom to Dave Scribner Regarding Comet Manufacturing Negotiation and National Labor Relations Board, November 20, 1947; 27.
      - Bergstrom to Sidney Gilbert Regarding Decca Negotiation, February 27, 1948; 28.
      - Bergstrom to Gilbert Regarding Decca Negotiation, March 15, 1948; 29.
      - Bergstrom to Local 1227 Regarding Decca Negotiation, March 29, 1948; 30.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 5, 1949; 31.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Packinghouse Workers Strike, February 4, 1949; 32.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Butler Manufacturing Strike, March 26, 1949; 33.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits, October 22, 1949; 34.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Staff Members and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 13, 1950; 35.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, March 17, 1950; 36.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding 1950 UE Convention, August 17, 1950; 37.
      - Bergstrom to Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service Regarding Smith System Negotiation with Notice, April 4, 1951; 38.
      - Bergstrom to Fitzgerald Regarding Dues with Card, December 8, 1952; 39.
      - Bergstrom to Emspak Regarding Union Label, November 25, 1953; 40.
    - Local 1139 Reuben Carlson Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 119)
      - Ernest DeMaio to Reuben Carlson Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, War Labor Board, and No-Strike Pledge with Resolution, February 11, 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Carlson Regarding Dues, October 29, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Carlson Regarding Pittsburgh Meeting, April 15, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Carlson Regarding Wilson Rubber Organization, June 9, 1943; 4.
      - Norma Gould to Carlson Regarding Maico Organization, June 21, 1943; 5.
      - James Matles to Carlson Regarding Finances, July 7, 1943; 6.
      - Matles to Carlson Regarding Perfection Organization, July 16, 1943; 7.
    - Local 1139 Reuben Carlson Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 120)
      - Reuben Carlson to Julius Emspak Regarding Alabama Pipe and Gadsen Iron Wages, February 3, 1942; 1.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Officers, February 10, 1942; 2.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding ADT System Contract, February 25, 1942; 3.
      - Carlson to J.R. Steelman Regarding Twin City Steel Negotiation, March 12, 1942; 4.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Star Machine Contract and Organization, June 4, 1942; 5.
      - Carlson to Emspak Regarding Withdrawals, October 22, 1942; 6.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Decca Negotiation and Women, November 19, 1942; 7.
      - Carlson to Neil Brant Regarding Twin City Steel Negotiation, War Labor Board, and Arbitration, February 25, 1943; 8.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Decca Contract, March 24, 1943; 9.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Wilson Rubber Organization, June 8, 1943; 10.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Maico Organization, June 21, 1943; 11.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Onan and Sons Organization, July 10, 1943; 12.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Perfection Manufacturing Organization, July 16, 1943; 13.
      - Carlson to Matles Regarding Contracts and Negotiations, July 20, 1943; 14.
      - Carlson to Emspak Regarding Officers and 1943 UE Convention, July 28, 1943; 15.
      - Carlson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Headquarters, September 30, 1943; 16.
      - Carlson to Emspak Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation and WLB, February 1, 1944; 17.
      - Carlson to Emspak Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation and WLB, February 7, 1944; 18.
    - Local 1139 Tom Foley Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 121)
      - Julius Emspak to Tom Foley Regarding Supplies, January 5, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to Foley Regarding Flour City Ornamental and American Brake Shoe Organization, March 3, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Foley Regarding Brothers Boiler Contract, April 19, 1938; 3.
      - James Matles to Foley Regarding Hudson Manufacturing Strike, January 9, 1939; 4.
      - Matles to Foley Regarding United Auto Workers, January 19, 1939; 5.
      - Matles to Foley Regarding District 11, August 7, 1939; 6.
      - William Mitchell to Foley Regarding American Brake Shoe, Steelworkers Organizing Committee, and Brothers Boiler, January 27, 1938; 7.
      - Mitchell to Foley Regarding Bahlstrom Organization, March 19, 1938; 8.
      - Mitchell to Foley Regarding ABC Washer and Hart-Carter, July 5, 1938; 9.
    - Local 1139 Tom Foley Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 122)
      - Tom Foley to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, November 20, 1937; 1.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Unemployment, January 2, 1938; 2.
      - Foley to William Mitchell Regarding American Brake Shoe Organization, Steelworkers Organizing Committee, Brothers Boiler Negotiation, and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, January 25, 1938; 3.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Brothers Boiler Organization, SWOC, and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, February 10, 1938; 4.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Dahlstrom and Iron Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 12, 1938; 5.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding International Association of Machinists and Ironworkers Inter-union Rivalry and Organization at Flour City Ornamental and American Brake Shoe, February 21, 1938; 6.
      - Foley to James Carey Regarding Brothers Boiler Strike and Boilermakers Inter-union Rivalry, March 19, 1938; 7.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding Brothers Boiler Contract, April 14, 1938; 8.
      - Foley to James Matles Regarding North Star Specialty and Brothers Boiler Organization and Inter-union Rivalry with IAM and Ironworkers, April 19, 1938; 9.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding Brothers Boiler Contract, April 25, 1938; 10.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, May 27, 1938; 11.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Twentieth Century Brass Negotiation, June 11, 1938; 12.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Hart-Carter Negotiation, June 29, 1938; 13.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Usona Manufacturing Organization, July 19, 1938; 14.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Hudson Manufacturing Negotiation, November 29, 1938; 15.
      - Foley to Mitchell Regarding Butler Manufacturing Negotiation, January 5, 1939; 16.
      - Foley to Matles Regarding Hudson Manufacturing Strike, January 6, 1939; 17.
      - Foley to Matles Regarding Hudson Manufacturing Strike and Untied Auto Workers, January 17, 1939; 18.
      - Foley to Matles Regarding Brothers Boiler Negotiation, May 12, 1939; 19.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding Hart-Carter Negotiation, June 20, 1939; 20.
      - Foley to Matles Regarding District 11 and Per Capita, August 4, 1939; 21.
    - Local 1139 General Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1952 (Box 8, Folder 123)
      - Julius Emspak to Oscar Lindman Regarding Singer Strike, May 3, 1939; 1.
      - Emspak to Lindman Regarding Singer Strike, June 6, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to Lindman Regarding Local 1111 Strike, February 16, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to Hugo Benson Regarding Foundries and Factionalism, December 5, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Oscar Andell Regarding Dues and Veterans, April 23, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Enoch Johnson Regarding National Strike Fund, October 23, 1952; 6.
      - James Matles to Lee Bergstrom Regarding Officers, August 19, 1940; 7.
      - Clifford McAvoy to Clarence Hathaway Regarding Political Action, February 25, 1947; 8.
      - Stephan Reynolds to Local 1939 Regarding Comet Manufacturing Organization, October 31, 1947; 9.
    - Local 1139 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1952, undated (Box 8, Folder 124)
      - Oscar Andell to S. Towson Regarding Local 735 Negotiation, October 29, 1945; 1.
      - Andell to Julius Emspak Regarding Hudson Manufacturing Strike, November 21, 1945; 2.
      - Andell to Emspak Regarding Hart Carter Strike, December 19, 1945; 3.
      - Hugo Benson to James Carey Regarding Foundry Council, January 18, 1940; 4.
      - Benson to Emspak Regarding Foundries, Factionalism, and Molders Inter-union Rivalry, November 11, 1941; 5.
      - Lee Bergstrom to James Matles Regarding Womens Auxiliary, August 5, 1940; 6.
      - Bergstrom to Matles Regarding Womens Auxiliary and Local 616 with October 1940, Mrs. Carl Will Letter to Bergstrom, October 2, 1940; 7.
      - Bernice Guy to Emspak Regarding 1948 UE Convention, July 26, 1938; 8.
      - Guy to Robert Duitch Regarding Local 614 Strike, October 18, 1948; 9.
      - Guy to Matles Regarding Staff Members and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 17, 1950; 10.
      - Otto Hanson to Ernest DeMaio Regarding District 11, September 19, 1947; 11.
      - Clarence Hathaway to Emspak Regarding Bishman Manufacturing Strike with List of Strikers, October 8, 1946; 12.
      - Hathaway to DeMaio Regarding Lake Center and Coin Meter Organization, October 20, 1947; 13.
      - Hathaway to Matles Regarding Factionalism, November 29, 1948; 14.
      - Oscar Lindman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 6, 1937; 15.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 2, 1937; 16.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 8, 1938; 17.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 11, 1938; 18.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Brothers Boiler Strike, April 11, 1938; 19.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 13, 1938; 20.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Electrical Ships, March 3, 1939; 21.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Singer Strike, April 29, 1939; 22.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Singer Strike, June 2, 1939; 23.
      - Lindman to Emspak Regarding Local 1111, February 13, 1940; 24.
      - Norman Mattson to Matles Regarding Strike Fund, May 16, 1952; 25.
      - A.W. Petterson to UE News Regarding Separate Charter for Foundries, Factionalism, and Molders Inter-union Rivalry, October 1, 1941; 26.
      - Everett Roemer to Emspak Regarding Political Action, October 2, 1946; 27.
      - Arne Wanhala to Matles Regarding Separate Charter for Foundries and Factionalism, 28.
      - Recording Secretary to William Mitchell Regarding Contracts, August 16, 1938; 29.
      - Recording Secretary to Matles Regarding RR Howell Contract, May 22, 1939; 30.
    - Local 1139 Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 8, Folder 125-126)
    - Local 1139 Minneapolis Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Local 1139 Minneapolis Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
    - Local 1139 Minneapolis Shops Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Local 1139 Per Capita Reports, September 1937-July 1938 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Local 1139 Publications, 1938-1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - "Report of Vice President Gutridge" Leaflet Regarding Boilermakers Inter-union Rivalry, April 1938; 1.
      - "Former CIO Members Join IMFWU" Clipping, January 1939; 2.
      - Merchandiser Newspaper, April 1942; 3.
    - Local 1139 American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - William Mauseth to Julius Emspak, August 27, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Mauseth, August 30, 1937; 2.
      - Tom Foley to Emspak, September 1, 1937; 3.
      - Earl Martin to Flour City Ornamental, October 19, 1937; 4.
      - Ralph Helstein to Emspak, December 28, 1937; 5.
      - Organizational Report, January 1, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Helstein, January 7, 1938; 7.
      - W.J. McCain to B.G. Johnson, August 22, 1938; 8.
    - Local 1139 Foundry Strike, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Petition to J.F. Quest, August 30, 1940; 1.
      - Strike Committee Letter, August 30, 1940; 2.
    - Local 1139 Twentieth Century Brass Strike, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Douglas Hall to James Matles, October 4, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Hall, October 7, 1941; 2.
    - Local 1139 Separate Charter for Foundries, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Foundry Council Resolution, October 8, 1941; 1.
      - Arne Wanhala to Foundry Members, November 11, 1941; 2.
      - Ernie Roemer to Julius Emspak, November 11, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Roemer, December 5, 1941; 4.
    - Local 1139 Twentieth Century Brass Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Bea Bassin to Albert Fitzgerald, February 3, 1943; 1.
      - Douglas Hall to James Matles, September 7, 1943; 2.
      - Neil Brant to Hall, September 10, 1943; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, February 11, 1944; 4.
      - War Labor Board Order, June 14, 1944; 5.
      - Executive Order, September 9, 1944; 6.
      - Reuben Carlson Affidavit with Membership List, October 19, 1944; 7.
    - Local 1139 Hart-Carter Strike, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Douglas Hall to Lewis Schwellenbach, August 29, 1945; 1.
      - John Daly to Albert Fitzgerald, September 7, 1945; 2.
      - Daly to Hall, September 7, 1945; 3.
      - Report of Strike, October 2, 1945; 4.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, October 30, 1945; 5.
      - List of Strikers, October 30, 1945; 6.
      - Termination of Strike with Contract Excerpt, November 21, 1945; 7.
    - Local 1139 Postel Manufacturing Negotiations, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Douglas Hall to Lewis Schwellenbach, September 11, 1945; 1.
      - John Daly to Albert Fitzgerald, September 21, 1945; 2.
      - Daly to Hall, September 21, 1945; 3.
    - Local 1139 Hudson Manufacturing Strike, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Report of Strike, November 14, 1945; 1.
      - List of Strikers, November 22, 1945; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, November 22, 1945; 3.
      - Termination of Strike, March 2, 1946; 4.
    - Local 1139 Telex Strike, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio with June 4, 1946, R.W. Bergstrom Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, June 6, 1946; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, June 20, 1946; 2.
    - Local 1139 Hart-Carter Negotiations, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, August 9, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, August 21, 1946; 2.
    - Local 1139 Despatch Oven Strike, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Report of Strike, July 15, 1947; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, July 31, 1947; 2.
    - Local 1139 Twentieth Century Brass Strike, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, April 10, 1948; 1.
      - Report of Strike, April 12, 1948; 2.
      - Termination of Strike, June 18, 1948; 3.
    - Local 1139 Franklin Transformer Strike, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Report of Strike, July 22, 1948; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, August 26, 1948; 2.
    - Local 1139 Taft-Hartley Compliance, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Certificate of Union Officers, November 4, 1949; 1.
      - Distribution of Financial Data, November 8, 1949; 2.
      - Non-Communist Affidavits, November 9, 1949; 3.
      - Registration Form with Financial Statement, November 10, 1949; 4.
    - Local 1139 Brothers Boiler Strike, 1941-1951 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Anthony DeMaio to James Matles, June 4, 1941; 1.
      - Nat Spero to DeMaio, June 6, 1951; 2.
    - Local 1139 Correspondence and Notifications, 1940-1950 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - George Grega to John Brophy Regarding Steelworkers Organizing Committee, August 19, 1940; 1.
      - A.N. Towsen to Yelverton Cowheard Regarding Alabama Foundries, January 5, 1942; 2.
      - Status of Contracts, January 1943; 3.
      - Unsigned Letter to Neil Brant Regarding War Labor Board and Foundries, February 3, 1943; 4.
      - Ernest DeMaio to James Matles Regarding Onan and Sons Organization, June 30, 1943; 5.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Bradley Equipment, October 17, 1946; 6.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Perfection Manufacturing, October 17, 1946; 7.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Photoplating, November 25, 1946; 8.
      - Report of Strike Regarding Hoff Rubber, June 23, 1947; 9.
      - Charles Ryan to M.A. Nichols Regarding Comet Manufacturing, Taft-Hartley Affidavits, and National Labor Relations Board, November 19, 1947; 10.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding US Air Conditioning, April 1, 1948; 11.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Perfection Manufacturing, April 1, 1948; 12.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Toro Manufacturing, April 1, 1948; 13.